Finding Aid for the George Peabody College Photograph Collection
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Series XVI: Portraits
  - S
    - Sandlin, Susan
    - Santos, Juan F.
    - Santos, Rolando
    - Santos, Urbana M.
    - Sargent, Clifford H.
    - Sargent, S. D.
    - Sasser, Carol W.
    - Satterwhite, Duke
    - Satterwhite, Gay
    - Satterwhite, Martha
    - Sauciev, E. N.
    - Saunders, Will P.
    - Savage, Henry
    - Savage, Pauline
    - Saveland, Robert N.
    - Savels, John
    - Sawhill, Clarence
    - Sawyer, Felix
    - Sawyer, Fred
    - Sawyer, John
    - Sawyers, James C.
    - Sawyers, Martha
    - Sayers, Frances Clarke
    - Sayler, Sanford M.
    - Schaeffer, Agnes
    - Schmidt, Elizabeth
    - Schmidt, John F.
    - Schneller, Roland
    - Schueter, Elsie
    - Schuiling, John
    - Schuschnigg, Kurt von
    - Schutte, Elsbeth
    - Schwartz, William, Jr.
    - Scoggins, Phil
    - Scott, Carol
    - Scott, Charles E.
    - Scott, Louise
    - Scott, Matty
    - Scott, Robert
    - Scott, Willadene A.
    - Scott, Wilma Tate
    - Scully, Mark
    - Seabury, Ruth Isabel
    - Sealey, Romero Mitchell
    - Seaman, R.
    - Sears, Barnas
    - Seawell, W. H.
    - Seay, Edward W.
    - Seay, Frances
    - Seay, Gwen
    - Sefsik, Stephen
    - Selph, Betty
    - Selvey, Willa J.
    - Sensing, Thurman
    - Sergent, Montford
    - Setliff, E. G.
    - Sewell, Frances C.
    - Sewell, Martin
    - Shane, Milton L.
    - Shankle, George E.
    - Shannon, W. A.
    - Sharp, Adda Mai
    - Sharp, Ella Becky
    - Sharp, L. A.
    - Sharp, Vernon, Jr.
    - Shaver, Emily
    - Shaver, Jesse M.
    - Shaver
    - Shaw, John C.
    - Shaw, William H.
    - Sheaey, Elaine
    - Shearer, Allen
    - Shelby, Nancy
    - Shelton, A. C.
    - Shelton, Travis
    - Sherrill, Jimmie
    - Sherrill, Lynn
    - Sherrod, Charles C.
    - Shibama, Tazu (2)
    - Shibata, Sachiko
    - Shibawa, Jazu
    - Shih, Peter S. T.
    - Shipstone, Clarice Inez
    - Shores, Louis
    - Shover, Jayne
    - Shuler, Cecil M.
    - Shutt, John L.
    - Siler, Dorothy Sue
    - Silver, James W.
    - Simmons, I. F.
    - Simpson, Alfred D.
    - Sims, Jerry S.
    - Singh. Amarjit
    - Sir, Donna
    - Sittler, Joseph
    - Sitton, William Paul
    - Skaggs, Irene Murphy
    - Skeen
    - Skelton, Harold
    - Skinner, Marilyn
    - Slagie, Amanda
    - Sloan, Katherine E.
    - Sloan, Marjorie Minton
    - Sloane, W. L.
    - Smart, Wyatt Aiken
    - Smith, Annie Green
    - Smith, Annie Sue
    - Smith, Arthur, Jr.
    - Smith, Barbara Anne
    - Smith, Bert R.
    - Smith, C. B.
    - Smith, C. C.
    - Smith, Daniel L
    - Smith, E. K.
    - Smith, E. Kirby
    - Smith, Ellison M.
    - Smith, Estelle Scroggin
    - Smith, Gladys
    - Smith, Hoke
    - Smith, Ida B.
    - Smith, J. L.
    - Smith, J. M.
    - Smith, James
    - Smith, James D.
    - Smith, James L.
    - Smith, Judy
    - Smith, Ken
    - Smith, L. I.
    - Smith, Lois
    - Smith, Margaret Chase
    - Smith, Mildred Ann
    - Smith, Nellie Angel
    - Smith, Norma
    - Smith, Payson
    - Smith, Q. M.
    - Smith, Richard
    - Smith, Samuel L.
    - Smith, T. E.
    - Smith, T. V.
    - Smith
    - Snavely, Tipton R.
    - Snelling, Vera
    - Snodgrass, Thomas Wood
    - Snoke, James S.
    - Snow, Miriam
    - Snow, Silas D.
    - Snow
    - Sokol, Thomas A.
    - Soon, Lee Won
    - Soucier, Blanche Connelly
    - South, Marie
    - Southall, Maycie Katherine
    - Southerlin, W. B.
    - Sowell, F. B.
    - Spache, George D.
    - Spain, Charles R.
    - Spaulding, Kenneth
    - Speal, Lucille R.
    - Speight, Walter
    - Spencer, Terrel
    - Spelman, J. E.
    - Sperling, Helen M.
    - Spurgeon, Vivian
    - Stack, J.
    - Stackhouse, Robert Edgar
    - Stackhouse, Wade D.
    - Stackhouse, Will
    - Stalcup, Mary Frances
    - Stalker, Varna G.
    - Stallworth, Hugh
    - Stallworth, Mrs. Hugh
    - Stanley, Raymond
    - Stanley, T. H.
    - Staples, Thomas S.
    - Stapleton, Irene
    - Stark, Lucien
    - Starls, C. N.
    - Starr, Richard
    - Stearns, Eben
    - Stearns, Eben S.
    - Steel, Marshall T.
    - Steele, A. M.
    - Steeutz, Hugh
    - Stehr, Bennie W.
    - Stein, Edwin E.
    - Stephens, Darleen Bell
    - Stephens, Elizabeth
    - Stephens, Genter L.
    - Stephens, Evelyn
    - Sternheimer, Stephen
    - Sterrett, Delbert
    - Sterrett, Marvin D.
    - Stetch, Lorena
    - Stewart, Lawrence Russell
    - Stewart, Randall
    - Stockard, Dick
    - Stockton, Kathryn
    - Stoddard, Alexander J.
    - Stoddard, Burt
    - Stoddard, George Dinsmore
    - Stoddard, Hugh T.
    - Stoddard, J. A.
    - Stokes, Elizabeth H.
    - Stokes, Jackie
    - Stokes, Walter
    - Stone, W. B.
    - Storm, A. V.
    - Storrie, Elizabeth
    - Stover, Eugenia
    - Stowe, Loraine Hunter
    - Strayer, George D., Jr.
    - Strayhorn, Elizabeth
    - Strickland, Wayne
    - Strickler, Robert P.
    - Stringer, Harold
    - Strobel, Eugene F.
    - Stroud, Annie Ruth
    - Stuart, Jesse (2)
    - Stuart, June
    - Stubbs
    - Studlien, Helen Settlemire
    - Stuntz
    - Sudduth, Solon
    - Suhr, Myong Won
    - Sullivan, Algernon Sydney
    - Sullivan
    - Sundt, Loretta Jean Porter
    - Sutherland, R. E. L.
    - Sutton, Frank
    - Suzzalls, Henry
    - Svec, M. Melvina
    - Swann, Arthur W.
    - Sweeney, Mack D.
    - Swift, Marjorie
    - Swint, Henry Lee
    - Swirtger, J. A.
  - T
    - Tabor, Dean C.
    - Taft, Charles P.
    - Tag, Herbert G.
    - Tait, Blanche
    - Talley, Milton B.
    - Tamotsu, Akinori
    - Tankard, George G., Jr.
    - Tansil, Blanche
    - Tansil, Rebecca
    - Tarver, Julie Reynolds
    - Tatum, Syble
    - Tavener, Eugene
    - Taylor, Edith
    - Taylor, Henry J.
    - Taylor, Hoy
    - Taylor, James Woodall
    - Taylor, Michael
    - Taylor, Wilburn
    - Teel, Frances
    - Temple, Ruth Hines
    - Templin, Margaret Jane
    - Terral, Children
    - Terrebourne, L. P.
    - Terrell, Fred
    - Terrell, M. T.
    - Terry, Dell
    - Thomas, Beulah
    - Thomas, Charles
    - Thomas, Jesse B.
    - Thomas, L. Roscoe
    - Thomas, T. Donley
    - Thomas, William N.
    - Thomas
    - Thomasson
    - Thompson, A. Guy
    - Thompson, Hallie
    - Thompson, John B.
    - Thompson, Kathy
    - Thompson, Maibeth
    - Thompson, Sally
    - Thomson, Robert
    - Thorndike, Edward L.
    - Thurston, Lee M.
    - Tidwell, Sam B.
    - Tiffany
    - Tillman, Mrs. J. Fount
    - Timberlake, Mary E.
    - Tinder, Frank N.
    - Tipton, Ed M.
    - Tison, W. W.
    - Tittman, George F.
    - Todd, L. O.
    - Tomlinson, Gus
    - Toomey, Delma G.
    - Torrance, Paul
    - Touster, Eva
    - Touchstone, T. N.
    - Tower, Wesley
    - Toy, Henry
    - Trice, John A.
    - Trousdale, Mattie Sue
    - Trythall, Gil
    - Tsai, Tehpen
    - Tuck, Marjorie
    - Tucker, E. B.
    - Tucker, L. L.
    - Tucker, Ruth
    - Tudon, H. B.
    - Tulock, Mary
    - Tupper, Vernon
    - Turner, Betsy Gebhart
    - Turner, Floyd V.
    - Turner, H. L.
    - Turner, Lucile
    - Turner, Mona
    - Turner, Reba
    - Turner, Robert
    - Turpin, N. C.
    - Tustin, L. T.
    - Tuttle, Elsie F.
    - Tyler, James W.
    - Tyler, Ralph
  - U
    - Underwood, Adele
    - Urner, D. M.
    - Urwin, E. Clifford
  - V
    - Valliniemi, Maija-Liisa
    - Vance, Berlin
    - Vance, Mrs. Berlin
    - Vance, Zeb B.
    - Van Clerr, Charles
    - Vanderkooi, David
    - Van Doren, Carl
    - Van Dullemen, Johanna J.
    - Van Dusen, Henry
    - Van Sickle, Joseph L.
    - Varney, Bernice Reaney
    - Vaughan, Eva
    - Vaughn, Lila F.
    - Velinsky, Stanislav
    - Viereck, Peter
    - Vigus
    - Vincent
    - Vining, Bill
    - Vitus, Bob
    - Voss, Elizabeth
  - W
    - Wade, Emma Hayes
    - Wade, Frances
    - Wade, Mrs. Seawright
    - Wafford, Azile
    - Walker, Charles H.
    - Walker, Franklin Trenaby
    - Walker, Kirby
    - Walker, Moddelle
    - Wall, Catherine
    - Walters, John Bennett
    - Wanamaker, Pearl A.
    - Ward
    - Warren, Eva
    - Warren, James T.
    - Warren, Mary
    - Warren, Mary Frances
    - Warren, Richard
    - Warren, Tom
    - Warren
    - Warriner, E. C.
    - Warwick, Richard Nason
    - Waters, Hugh
    - Watson, Barbara
    - Watson, E. H.
    - Watson, Georgia
    - Wattenbarger, James
    - Watts, Charles
    - Watts, Talmage Mims
    - Weaver, Charles
    - Weaver, Herbert
    - Weaver
    - Webb, A. C.
    - Webb, Gisela
    - Webb, George
    - Webb, Hanor
    - Webber
    - Wedgeworth, Ola
    - Weedon, Vivian
    - Weekiser, Ralph
    - Weeks, Edward
    - Weems, Don
    - Weinman, Arthur
    - Weinstein, Laura
    - Welch, Betty J.
    - Wells, J.
    - Wells, Laura Jane
    - West, Arthur C.
    - West, Joe Young
    - West, Pearl
    - Westerfield, James E.
    - Wharton, Kate
    - Wheeler, L. R.
    - Wheeler, Sallie C.
    - Wherry, Mary Lillian
    - Whetmore, George Peabody
    - Whitaker, Carolyn
    - Whitaker, Thomas
    - White, Barbara Ann
    - White, Betty Jane
    - White, Charles Henry
    - White, Esther Snavely
    - White, Florence
    - White Frank
    - White, Harriet Louise
    - White, J. B.
    - White, Josh, Jr.
    - White, Robert
    - White, Rosann
    - White, W. T.
    - Whitehead, Guy, III.
    - Whitehurst, Billie Burke
    - Whitesel, Ivan Lee
    - Whitley, S. H.
    - Whitlock, James
    - Whitlow, Floyd B., Jr.
    - Whitmer, J. R.
    - Whitmore, B. E.
    - Whitson, Millie
    - Whitt, Mrs. Wayne
    - Wick, Carol Eileen
    - Wigerink
    - Wiggin, Gladys
    - Wiggins, Doris
    - Wight, Edward A.
    - Wilcoxon, Fred H.
    - Wilcoxon, Hardy
    - Wilder, Rebecca Louise
    - Wilgus, Ruth
    - Wilkes, J. T.
    - Wilkins, Martha Anne
    - Willeford, Jack A.
    - Willers, Jack
    - Willey, Warner W.
    - Williams, Carol
    - Williams, Corinne June
    - Williams, Dorothy K.
    - Williams, E. L.
    - Williams, Eunice L.
    - Williams, Flournoy Elizabeth
    - Williams, Geannie S.
    - Williams, Gladys
    - Williams, Henry N.
    - Williams, Ida F.
    - Williams, Margaret
    - Williams, Rufie Lee
    - Williams, Sarah Pierman
    - Williams, Sharon Ann
    - Williams, Shirley Joy
    - Williams, Wiley
    - Williams
    - Williams
    - Willis, Aubrey S.
    - Willis, Diane Janice
    - Willis, L. J.
    - Willoughby, Iris Ann
    - Wills, Guy H.
    - Wilson, Ann Marie
    - Wilson, Betty
    - Wilson, Frances Seay
    - Wilson, Gilbert
    - Wilson, Gypsy
    - Wilson, John C.
    - Wilson, Leland
    - Wilson, Mary C.
    - Wilson, Rosemary G.
    - Wilson, Roy K.
    - Wilson, W. M.
    - Wilson
    - Windrow, J. E.
    - Wingler
    - Winoker, S.
    - Winstead, Betty Lou
    - Winthrop, Grenville Lindall
    - Wireman, Billy O.
    - Wirth, Edward
    - Wirth, F. P.
    - Witengier, Mariann
    - Withrow, Scott
    - Witte, Angelyn
    - Witty, Elaine Paige
    - Witty, Paul
    - Wojtusik, Florence
    - Wolcott, Leonard T.
    - Wolery, Robert Carl
    - Wolfe, Irving
    - Wolfe, Mary Agnes
    - Womack, Clarice Kiser
    - Womack, J. P.
    - Womack, Ray
    - Womack, Richard Elwood
    - Womack, Roberta Sue
    - Wood, C. R.
    - Wood, Chester
    - Wood, James
    - Wood, Phyllis T.
    - Woodall, Robbie
    - Woodard, Roy
    - Woodard, Thomas
    - Woodley, Cornett
    - Woodley, Robert Earl
    - Woodruff, Beverly J.
    - Woods, B. J.
    - Woods, Carl Neal
    - Woodward, Claudia Marie
    - Woodward, Jim
    - Woodward, Judy Coble
    - Woodward, Mrs. Theodore
    - Woody, Joseph Rennie, Jr.
    - Wooster, Thomas Jackson
    - Worf, Wendell
    - Workman, Ann
    - Workman, J. H.
    - Workman, Mary Elizabeth
    - Workman, Virginia
    - Worrell, Norman
    - Worthy, H. D.
    - Wray, E. H.
    - Wright, E. A.
    - Wright, Frederick Woodside
    - Wright, Logan
    - Wright, Nora Ann
    - Wright, Pat
    - Wrightsman, Lawrence
    - Wu, Daisy
    - Wyman, Bill
    - Wynn, William T
  - Y
    - Yang, Y. C.
    - Yearwood, Joy
    - Yearwood, Miranda Elizabeth
    - Yelton, Carolyn Lee
    - Yelton
    - Yeng, Charles Chih-Hung
    - Ying, Harriet C.
    - Yong, Kai C.
    - Young, Audrey
    - Young, Carol Jean
    - Young, Carol Sue
    - Young, James W.
    - Young, Mrs. James W.
    - Young, Mary Alice
    - Young, Norvell
    - Young, Troy G.
    - Young, Victor Chao-Ing
    - Young, Wayne
    - Young, Wilbur S.
    - Youngblood, Karen E.
    - Yount, M. H.
    - Youell, D. H.
    - Yuen, Wong Lai
  - Z
    - Zander, Sue
    - Zapoleon, Margaerite
    - Zeigenfus
    - Zeis
    - Zepernick, Werner
    - Zook, George F.
  - Unidentified
    - Individuals (22)
    - Families (3)
- Series XVII: University of Nashville
  - Athletics
  - Buildings (4)
  - Classroom Scenes
  - Faculty
  - Group Photographs
  - Portraits
  - Presidents
  - Student Activities
  - Trolley